<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Home Workout</string>
    <string name="slogan">Commit to be fit ...</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    //About Us
    <string name="about_info">Application Information</string>
    <string name="app_info">\n\tWe want to help you live a fit and healthy lifestyle! We do this by providing you many such workouts. We believe that building a positive culture is incredibly important. \n\n\tWe work hard to ensure we have strong relationships with our customers, bringing you the best possible workouts. We are an ambitious company and we’re always looking for great people to join our team. \n\n\tWe combine different types of fitness exercises to meet different fitness needs and levels. Our awesome team is always keen to help, so please call us to discuss your needs.\n</string>
    <string name="about_team">Contributors</string>
    <string name="contribution">\tGaikwad Dipak\n\tHambir Akshay\n\tGandhi Kalpesh\n\tChavhan Shantanu\n</string>

    // MENU items
    <string name="Workout">Workout</string>
    <string name="Timer">Stop Watch</string>

    //WORKOUT COURSES
    <string name="wieght_loss_workout">Wieght Loss Workout</string>
    <string name="full_body_workout">Full Body Workout</string>
    <string name="lower_body_workout">Lower Body Workout</string>
    <string name="chest_beginner">Chest Workout For Beginner</string>
    <string name="chest_intermediate">Chest Workout For Intermediate</string>
    <string name="chest_advance">Chest Workout For Advance</string>
    <string name="abs_beginner">ABS Workout For Beginner</string>
    <string name="abs_intermediate">ABS Workout For Intermediate</string>
    <string name="abs_advance">ABS Workout For Advance</string>
    <string name="arm_beginner">Arm Workout For Beginner</string>
    <string name="arm_intermediate">Arm Workout For Intermediate</string>
    <string name="arm_advance">Arm Workout For Advance</string>
    <string name="shoulder_and_back_beginner">Shoulder And Back Workout For Beginner</string>
    <string name="shoulder_and_back_intermediate">Shoulder And Back Workout For Intermediate</string>
    <string name="shoulder_and_back_advance">Shoulder And Back Workout For Advance</string>
    <string name="leg_beginner">Leg Workout For Beginner</string>
    <string name="leg_intermediate">Leg Workout For Intermediate</string>
    <string name="leg_advance">Leg Workout For Advance</string>

    //WORKOUTS NAME
    <string name="abdominal_crunches">Abdominal Crunches</string>
    <string name="arm_scissors">Arm Scissors</string>
    <string name="backward_lunges">Backward Lunges</string>
    <string name="bicycle_crunches">Bicycle Crunches</string>
    <string name="burpees">Burpees</string>
    <string name="cobra_stretch">Cobra Stretch</string>
    <string name="forward_lunges">Forward Lunges</string>
    <string name="inchworms">Inchworms</string>
    <string name="jumping_jack">Jumping Jack</string>
    <string name="jumping_squats">Jumping Squats</string>
    <string name="mountain_climbers">Mountain Climbers</string>
    <string name="push_ups">Push Ups</string>
    <string name="side_hop">Side Hop</string>
    <string name="skipping_without_rope">Skipping Without Rope</string>
    <string name="squats">Squats</string>
    <string name="incline_push_ups">Incline Push Ups</string>
    <string name="box_push_ups">Box Push Ups</string>
    <string name="knee_push_ups">Knee Push Ups</string>
    <string name="wide_arm_push_ups">Wide Arm Push Ups</string>
    <string name="chest_stertch">Chest Stertch</string>
    <string name="side_lying_leg_lift_left">Side Lying Leg Lift Left</string>
    <string name="side_lying_leg_lift_right">Side Lying Leg Lift Right</string>
    <string name="donkey_kicks_left">Donkey Kicks Left</string>
    <string name="donkey_kicks_right">Donkey Kicks Right</string>
    <string name="left_quad_stretch_with_wall">Left Quad Stretch With Wall</string>
    <string name="right_quad_stretch_with_wall">Right Quad Stretch With Wall</string>
    <string name="knee_to_chest_stretch_left">Knee To Chest Stretch Left</string>
    <string name="knee_to_chest_stretch_right">Knee To Chest Stretch Right</string>
    <string name="hindu_push_ups">Hindu Push Ups</string>
    <string name="staggered_push_ups">Staggered Push Ups</string>
    <string name="push_ups_and_rotation">Push Ups And Rotation</string>
    <string name="decline_push_ups">Decline Push Ups</string>
    <string name="spiderman_push_ups">Spiderman Push Ups</string>
    <string name="russian_twist">Russian Twist</string>
    <string name="heel_touch">Heel Touch</string>
    <string name="leg_raises">Leg Raises</string>
    <string name="plank">Plank</string>
    <string name="spine_lumber_twist_strech_left">Spine Lumber Twist Strech Left</string>
    <string name="spine_lumber_twist_strech_right">Spine Lumber Twist Strech Right</string>
    <string name="crossover_crunch">Crossover Crunch</string>
    <string name="side_bridges_left">Side Bridges Left</string>
    <string name="side_bridges_right">Side Bridges Right</string>
    <string name="butt_bridge">Butt Bridge</string>
    <string name="v_up">V-Up</string>
    <string name="side_plank_left">Side Plank Left</string>
    <string name="side_plank_right">Side Plank Right</string>
    <string name="sit_ups">Sit Ups</string>
    <string name="arm_raises">Arm Raises</string>
    <string name="side_arm_raises">Side Arm Raises</string>
    <string name="triceps_dips">Triceps Dips</string>
    <string name="arm_circles_clockwise">Arm Circles Clockwise</string>
    <string name="arm_circles_counter_clockwise">Arm Circles Counter Clockwise</string>
    <string name="diamond_push_ups">Diamond Push Ups</string>
    <string name="leg_barbell_curl_left">Leg Barbell Curl Left</string>
    <string name="leg_barbell_curl_right">Leg Barbell Curl Right</string>
    <string name="diagonal_plank">Diagonal Plank</string>
    <string name="wall_push_ups">Wall Push Ups</string>
    <string name="triceps_stretch_left">Triceps Stretch Left</string>
    <string name="triceps_stretch_right">Triceps Stretch Right</string>
    <string name="standing_biceps_stretch_left">Standing Biceps Stretch Left</string>
    <string name="standing_biceps_stretch_right">Standing Biceps Stretch Right</string>
    <string name="floor_triceps_dips">Floor Triceps Dips</string>
    <string name="military_push_ups">Military Push Ups</string>
    <string name="alternating_hooks">Alternating Hooks</string>
    <string name="arm_curl_crunch_left">Arm Curl Crunch Left</string>
    <string name="arm_curl_crunch_right">Arm Curl Crunch Right</string>
    <string name="shoulder_gators">Shoulder Gators</string>
    <string name="doorway_curls_left">Doorway Curls Left</string>
    <string name="doorway_curls_right">Doorway Curls Right</string>
    <string name="modified_push_ups_low_hold">Modified Push Ups Low Hold</string>
    <string name="rhomboid_pulls">Rhomboid Pulls</string>
    <string name="side_lying_floor_strerch_left">Side Lying Floor Strerch Left</string>
    <string name="side_lying_floor_strerch_right">Side Lying Floor Strerch Right</string>
    <string name="cat_cow_pose">Cat Cow Pose</string>
    <string name="reclined_rhomboid_squeezes">Reclined Rhomboid Squeezes</string>
    <string name="childs_pose">Childs Pose</string>
    <string name="triceps_kickbacks">Triceps Kickbacks</string>
    <string name="hip_hinge">Hip Hinge</string>
    <string name="hover_push_ups">Hover Push Ups</string>
    <string name="swimmer_and_superman">Swimmer And Superman</string>
    <string name="hyperextension">Hyperextension</string>
    <string name="pike_push_ups">Pike Push Ups</string>
    <string name="reverse_push_ups">Reverse Push Ups</string>
    <string name="supine_push_ups">Supine Push Ups</string>
    <string name="reverse_snow_angels">Reverse Snow Angels</string>
    <string name="wall_calf_raises">Wall Calf Raises</string>
    <string name="sumo_squat_calf_raises_with_wall">Sumo Squat Calf Raises With Wall</string>
    <string name="calf_stretch_left">Calf Stretch Left</string>
    <string name="calf_stretch_right">Calf Stretch Right</string>
    <string name="fire_hydrant_left">Fire Hydrant Left</string>
    <string name="fire_hydrant_right">Fire Hydrant Right</string>
    <string name="lunges">Lunges</string>
    <string name="side_leg_circles_left">Side Leg Circles Left</string>
    <string name="side_leg_circles_right">Side Leg Circles Right</string>
    <string name="sumo_squat">Sumo Squat</string>
    <string name="reverse_flutter_kicks">Reverse Flutter Kicks</string>
    <string name="wall_sit">Wall Sit</string>
    <string name="calf_raise_with_splayed_foot">Calf Raise With Splayed Foot</string>
    <string name="single_leg_calf_hop_left">Single Leg Calf Hop Left</string>
    <string name="single_leg_calf_hop_right">Single Leg Calf Hop Right</string>
    <string name="bottom_leg_lift_left">Bottom Leg Lift Left</string>
    <string name="bottom_leg_lift_right">Bottom Leg Lift Right</string>
    <string name="curtsy_lunges">Curtsy Lunges</string>
    <string name="glute_kick_back_left">Glute Kick Back Left</string>
    <string name="glute_kick_back_right">Glute Kick Back Right</string>
    <string name="lying_butterfly_stretch">Lying Butterfly Stretch</string>
    <string name="leaning_stretcher_raises">Leaning Stretcher Raises</string>
    <string name="wall_resisting_single_leg_calf_raise_left">Wall Resisting Single Leg Calf Raise Left</string>
    <string name="wall_resisting_single_leg_calf_raise_right">Wall Resisting Single Leg Calf Raise Right</string>

    //Workout Steps
    <string name="abdominal_crunches_step">\n1.	Lie on your back with your knees bent and your arms stretched forward.\n2.	Then lift your upper body off the floor. Hold for a few seconds and slowly return. It primarily works the rectus abdomens muscle and the oblique.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_scissors_step">\n1.	Stand upright with your feet should wide apart.\n2.	Stretch your arms in front of you at shoulder height with one arm overlap the other in the shape of the letter ‘X’, and then spread them apart.\n3.	Switch arms, and repeat the exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="backward_lunges_step">\n1.	Stand tall with your hip distance apart.\n2.	Take a large step backward and lower your body toward the floor. Both legs should be bent at a 90-degree angle at the bottom of the lunge. Rise back to start and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="bicycle_crunches_step">\n1.	Start on your back with your hands behind your head. Lift your right knee toward your chest with your left leg straight and lifted a few inches up.\n2.	Lift your upper body up. Draw your knee to the opposite elbow, alternating sides.\n</string>
    <string name="burpees_step">\n1.	Begin in a standing position. Sit into a squat and place your hands on ground outside your feet.\n2.	Kick both feet outside you and land in push up position, keep the hips up and core engage. Take the chest to the ground at the bottom of the push up. Press up from the bottom of push up and return feet to hands.\n3.	Return to standing by jumping off the ground, clapping hands overhead.\n</string>
    <string name="cobra_stretch_step">\n1.	To begin the pose lie flat on the floor with your belly facing down and place your hands underneath the shoulders.\n2.	Tense your legs, contract your thighs and press feet firmly into the floor.\n3.	Then push your chest up off the ground as far as possible.\n</string>
    <string name="forward_lunges_step">\n1.	Step forward with a leg and bend it until both legs are in a 90 degree angle.\n2.	Push through your front heel to activate your glutes and back to the starting position.\n</string>
    <string name="inchworms_step">\n1.	Stand tall and down until your hands reach the floor. Walk your hands forward until you’re one long line in a plank position.\n2.	Take tiny steps walking your feet forward until they reach your hands. Walk hands out to plank again, and feet backs to hands.\n</string>
    <string name="jumping_jack_step">\n1.	Begin by standing with your legs straight and your arms to your sides.\n2.	Jump up and spread your feet beyond hip width apart while building your arms above your head, nearly touching.\n3.	Jump again, lowering your arms and bringing your legs together.\n</string>
    <string name="jumping_squats_step">\n1.	Start in a squat position, then jump using your abdominal muscles for strength. This exercise works for your abdomen.\n</string>
    <string name="mountain_climbers_step">\n1.	Make your knees as high as you can. Keep your head straight with your waist in a steady horizontal position.\n2.	Screw your hands into the floor to create a tension and solid upper body. Your elbows and biceps should face forward.\n</string>
    <string name="push_ups_step">\n1.	Place your hands slightly wider than your shoulders. Bend your arms until your chest almost touches the ground.\n2.	Maintain a straight body throughout the movement. Make it easier by  placing your knees on the ground.\n3.	Screw your hands into the floor to create a tension and solid upper body. Your elbows and biceps should face forward.\n</string>
    <string name="side_hop_step">\n1.	Stand on the floor, put your hands in front you and hop side to side.\n</string>
    <string name="skipping_without_rope_step">\n1.	Place your arms at your sides and pretend to hold a skipping rope handle in each hand.\n2.	Jump and alternately land on the balls of your feet, rotating your wrists at the same time as if you were spinning a rope.\n</string>
    <string name="squats_step">\n1.	Stand straight with feet hip width apart. Stand with your feet apart, directly under your hips.\n2.	Standing up tall, put your shoulders back, lift up your chest and pull in your abdominal muscles.\n3.	Bend your knees while keeping your upper body as straight as possible. Lower yourself as far as you can without leaning your upper body more than few inches forward.\n4.	Being careful not to lock your knees when you reach a standing position, straighten your legs. Repeat the movement.\n</string>
    <string name="incline_push_ups_step">\n1.	Place your hands slightly wider than shoulder-width apart on a bench or other stable, elevated surface and assume a high plank position with your feet together and body straight from head to heels.\n2.	Keeping your back flat and core engaged, lower your chest to within a few inches of the benches.\n3.	Pause, and then push yourself back up to starting position.\n</string>
    <string name="box_push_ups_step">\n1.	Start on all fours with your knees under your butt and your hands directly under your shoulders.\n2.	Bend your elbows and do a push-up.\n3.	Return to the start position and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="knee_push_ups_step">\n1.	Start in the regular push-up position, then let your knees touch the floor and raise your feet up off the floor.\n2.	Next push your body up and down.\n</string>
    <string name="wide_arm_push_ups_step">\n1.	Begin in your top of push-up position with your arms straight and your wrist underneath your shoulders.\n2.	Step each hand a few inches wider. As you inhale, bend your elbows out to the sides as you lower your torso toward the floor.\n</string>
    <string name="chest_stertch_step">\n1.	Stand in middle of a doorway with one foot in front of the other. Bend your elbows to a 90-degree angle and place your forearms on each side of the doorway.\n2.	Shift your leg onto your front leg, leaning forward until you feel a stretch in your chest muscles. Hold this position for 20 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="side_lying_leg_lift_left_step">\n1.	Lie down on your right arm. The arm that’s closest to the floor shoulder while your left arm is bent with your hand on your hip. Your legs should be extended and stacked on top of one another.\n2.	Slowly raise your left leg as high as you can. Pause, and then return to the starting position.\n</string>
    <string name="side_lying_leg_lift_right_step">\n1.	Lie down on your left arm. The arm that’s closest to the floor shoulder while your right arm is bent with your hand on your hip. Your legs should be extended and stacked on top of one another.\n2.	Slowly raise your right leg as high as you can. Pause, and then return to the starting position.\n</string>
    <string name="donkey_kicks_left_step">\n1.	Start on all fours with your knees under your butt and your hands under your shoulders.\n2.	Then lift your left leg and squeeze your butt as much as you can. Go back to the start position and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="donkey_kicks_right_step">\n1.	Start on all fours with your knees under your butt and your hands under your shoulders.\n2.	Then lift your right leg and squeeze your butt as much as you can. Go back to the start position and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="left_quad_stretch_with_wall_step">\n1.	Stand with your side to the wall, placing a right hand on the wall for balance.\n2.	Hold your left foot with your left hand and lift the foot up toward your rear end, keeping your thighs and knees together. Hold this position.\n</string>
    <string name="right_quad_stretch_with_wall_step">\n1.	Stand with your side to the wall, placing a right hand on the wall for balance.\n2.	Hold your right foot with your right hand and lift the foot up toward your rear end, keeping your thighs and knees together. Hold this position.\n</string>
    <string name="knee_to_chest_stretch_left_step">\n1.	Lie on your back with your knees bent. Bring left knee into your hands and gently let your arms pull your knee toward your chest.\n2.	Hold this position for 30 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="knee_to_chest_stretch_right_step">\n1.	Lie on your back with your knees bent. Bring right knee into your hands and gently let your arms pull your knee toward your chest.\n2.	Hold this position for 30 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="hindu_push_ups_step">\n1.	Start with your feet and hands a little more than shoulder width apart, forming your body into an upside down ‘V’ and keeping your head, neck and spine aligned. The arms are touching the ears in this position.\n2.	Bend your elbows and lower your chest down and forward. Keep pushing forward and up until your body is in the cobra position. From there, push your body straight back to the starting position and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="staggered_push_ups_step">\n1.	Start in push-up position with your body in a straight line from your shoulders to your ankles. Stagger your heads. Place one hand slightly forward while the remains under your shoulders.\n2.	Lower your body so your elbows are 90 degrees ans return to starting position. Switch other hand in front and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="push_ups_and_rotation_step">\n1.	Engage your core as you twist your torso. As one hand is supporting your body move the other straight above your head.\n2.	Keep both arms in line with each other and your shoulders. Make it easier by placing your knees on the ground.\n</string>
    <string name="decline_push_ups_step">\n1.	Place your feet on a bench or a raised platform and get into the pushup position with your hands slightly wider than shoulder width apart.\n2.	With your feet on the bench and your arms holding your body up, begin exercise by lowering yourself down to the ground while keeping your entire body in a straight line.\n3.	Lower your chest as close to the ground as you can, pause, then push yourself back to starting position.\n</string>
    <string name="spiderman_push_ups_step">\n1.	Get into push-up position with your shoulders over your wrists and your body is one line from your shoulders to your ankles.\n2.	Lower down to the bottom of push-ups. As  you do so , draw your right knee up toward your right elbow keeping your thigh parallel with ground.\n3.	As you press up , strengthen your right leg and return your right foot to the floor. Repeat on the other side.\n</string>
    <string name="russian_twist_step">\n1.	Sit on the floor with your knees bent , feet lifted a little bit and back titled backwards.\n2.	Then hold your hands together and twist from side to side.\n</string>
    <string name="heel_touch_step">\n1.	Lie down with your back on the ground and your knees bent and pointed towards the ceiling. With your arms on your side raise your shoulders slightly off the ground.\n2.	Using your abs rotate your right hand down to your right foot and then back up. Then do the same thing with your left hand.\n</string>
    <string name="leg_raises_step">\n1.	Lay down with your back flat on the floor , feet straight out and together and your hands on your side.\n2.	While keep your legs as straight as you can lift your feet up in the air between 6-12 inches.\n3.	You can either hold for designated period of time or you can raise them up and then lower them right back down. This completes one repetition.\n</string>
    <string name="plank_step">\n1.	Start in a pushup position with your hands directly under your shoulders.\n2.	Bend your elbows and lower yourself down until you can shift your weight from your hands to your forearms. Contract your abs and glutes. Hold for up to 20 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="spine_lumber_twist_strech_left_step">\n1.	Lie on your back with your legs extended.\n2.	Lift your leg up and use your right hand to pull your left knee to the right , but keep your other arm extended to the side on the floor.\n3.	Hold this position for 30 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="spine_lumber_twist_strech_right_step">\n1.	Lie on your back with your legs extended.\n2.	Lift your right leg up and use your left hand to pull your right knee to the left, but keep your other arm extended to the side on the floor.\n3.	Hold this position for a 30 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="crossover_crunch_step">\n1.	Lie on your knees bent and your hands behind your ears.\n2.	Raise and twist your torso so your right elbow moves to meet your left knee. Repeat with the other side.\n</string>
    <string name="side_bridges_left_step">\n1.	Lie on your right side. Use your right elbow to support upper body. Put your left hand on your waist.\n2.	Contract your core and raise your hips until your body is in a straight line from head to feet. Hold the position without letting your hips drop for the allotted time. Then go back to the start position and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="side_bridges_right_step">\n1.	Lie on your left side. Use your left elbow to support upper body. Put your right hand on your waist.\n2.	Contract your core and raise your hips until your body is in a straight line from head to feet. Hold the position without letting your hips drop for the allotted time. Then go back to the start position and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="butt_bridge_step">\n1.	Lie on your back with knees bent and feet flat on the floor. Put your arms flat at your sides. Then lift your butt up and down.\n</string>
    <string name="v_up_step">\n1.	Touch your toes with your hands at the top of movement. Maintain a straight back through the movement. Bend your knees for an easier option.\n</string>
    <string name="side_plank_left_step">\n1.	Lie on your left side with your forearm supporting your body. Hold your body in a straight line.\n</string>
    <string name="side_plank_right_step">\n1.	Lie on your right side with your forearm supporting your body. Hold your body in a straight line.\n</string>
    <string name="sit_ups_step">\n1.	Lie on your back and start with knees bent and feet on the mat. Arms are crossed and resting on the chest.\n2.	Bring chin to chest and flex, the head, neck, and torso off the mat coming to a seated position then return back down with control.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_raises_step">\n1.	Stand on the floor with your arms extended straight forward at shoulder height.\n2.	Raise your arms above your head. Return to the start position and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="side_arm_raises_step">\n1.	Stand with your feet shoulder width apart. Raise your arms to the sides at shoulders height, then put them down.\n2.	Repeat the exercise. Keep your arms straight during the exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="triceps_dips_step">\n1.	Squeeze your shoulder blades and lift your chest as you point your elbows straight back.\n2.	Lower your hips in vertical motion, maintaining a straight line from your back to neck. Keep your elbows tucked in behind you and your shoulders away from your ears.\n3.	Make it easier by moving your feet closer to the chair.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_circles_clockwise_step">\n1.	Stand on the floor with your arms extended straight out to the sides at shoulder height.\n2.	Move your arms clockwise in circles fast. Try to do it as fast as you can.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_circles_counter_clockwise_step">\n1.	Stand on the floor with your arms extended straight out to the sides at shoulder height.\n2.	Move your arms counterclockwise in circles fast. Try to do it as fast as you can.\n</string>
    <string name="diamond_push_ups_step">\n1.	Get on all fours with your hands together under your chest. Position your index fingers and thumbs so they are touching, forming a diamond shape, and extend your arms so that your body is elevated and forms a straight line from your head to your feet.\n2.	Lower your chest towards your hands, ensuring you don’t flare your elbows out to the sides and keeping your back flat. Stop just before your chest touches the floor, then push back up to the starting position.\n</string>
    <string name="leg_barbell_curl_left_step">\n1.	Stand against a wall. Lift your right leg up, lean forward and grab underneath your right ankle with your left hand.\n2.	Bring the ankle up towards the shoulder as much as you can, then lower it and repeat the exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="leg_barbell_curl_right_step">\n1.	Stand against a wall. Lift your left leg up, lean forward and grab underneath your left ankle with your right hand.\n2.	Bring the ankle up towards the shoulder as much as you can, then lower it and repeat the exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="diagonal_plank_step">\n1.	Start in straight arm plank position.\n2.	Lift your right arm and left leg until they are parallel with the ground. Return to the start position and repeat with the other side.\n</string>
    <string name="wall_push_ups_step">\n1.	Place your hands slightly wider than your shoulders. Slide your shoulders blades down your back, away from your ears.\n2.	Maintain a straight body throughout the movement. The further you move your feet away from the wall the harder it gets.\n</string>
    <string name="triceps_stretch_left_step">\n1.	Put your left hand on your back, use your right hand to grab your left elbow and gently pull it. Hold this position for 30 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="triceps_stretch_right_step">\n1.	Put your right hand on your back, use your left hand to grab your right elbow and gently pull it. Hold this position for 30 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="standing_biceps_stretch_left_step">\n1.	Stand with your left arm close to a wall. Extend your left arm and put your left hand on the wall, then gently turn your body to the right.\n</string>
    <string name="standing_biceps_stretch_right_step">\n1.	Stand with your right arm close to a wall. Extend your right arm and put your right hand on the wall, then gently turn your body to the left.\n</string>
    <string name="floor_triceps_dips_step">\n1.	Sit on floor with your knees bent, feet on floor, hands on floor behind you with fingers pointing toward body. To begin, lift hips off floor.\n2.	Slowly and gently bend your elbows and lower your body close to the floor and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="military_push_ups_step">\n1.	Start a push-up position with your hands directly under your hands directly under your shoulders and feet no more than 12 inches apart.\n2.	Bend your elbows and lower your body until your upper arms are parallel to floor. Stay in this position for one second and then push your body back to the starting position and repeat the exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="alternating_hooks_step">\n1.	Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart and place your dominant foot slightly forward. Slightly bend your elbows at 90 degrees.\n2.	Raise your right arm to shoulder height and keep your forearm parallel to ground. Rotate your shoulders and hips and punch towards the left. Switch slides and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_curl_crunch_left_step">\n1.	Lie on your left side with your knees bent and lifted. Grasp your left hand and put your right hand behind your head.\n2.	Then raise your upper body by pulling your left thigh. Repeat the exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_curl_crunch_right_step">\n1.	Lie on your right side with your knees bent and lifted. Grasp your right hand and put your left hand behind your head.\n2.	Then raise your upper body by pulling your right thigh. Repeat the exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="shoulder_gators_step">\n1.	Stand upright with your hands beside your ears and elbows facing each side. Rotate your elbows until both of them are facing the front.\n</string>
    <string name="doorway_curls_left_step">\n1.	Stand in a doorway. Grasp the doorframe using your left hand and put your feet close to the bottom of the door.\n2.	Extend your left arm and lean back, then pull at the doorframe and come back to the starting position. Repeat the exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="doorway_curls_right_step">\n1.	Stand in a doorway. Grasp the doorframe using your right hand and put your feet close to the bottom of the door.\n2.	Extend your right arm and lean back, then pull at the doorframe and come back to the starting position. Repeat the exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="modified_push_ups_low_hold_step">\n1.	Start in standard push-up position but with your feet shoulder-width apart and knees on the ground.\n2.	Lower your body until your elbows are at 90 degrees. Hold this position.\n</string>
    <string name="rhomboid_pulls_step">\n1.	Stand with your feet shoulder width apart. Raise your arms parallel to the ground and bend your elbows.\n2.	Pull your elbows back and squeeze your shoulder blades. Repeat this exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="side_lying_floor_strerch_left_step">\n1.	Lie on your right side with your right knees slightly bent in front of you and your left leg stretched behind the right leg.\n2.	Straighten your left arm over your head and gently pull on your left arm over your head and gently pull on your left wrist to stretch the left side of your body. Hold this position for 30 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="side_lying_floor_strerch_right_step">\n1.	Lie on your left side with your left knees slightly bent in front of you and your right leg stretched behind the left leg.\n2.	Straighten your right arm over your head and gently pull on your right arm over your head and gently pull on your right wrist to stretch the right side of your body. Hold this position for 30 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="cat_cow_pose_step">\n1.	On all fours, your knees should be hip with distance and your hands should be directly below your shoulders. Your spine is neutral here.\n2.	Inhale as you drop your belly and lift your gaze and your bone towards the sky.\n3.	Exhale and tighten your abs to scoop and curl your spline, moving your head and tailbone closer to each other.\n</string>
    <string name="reclined_rhomboid_squeezes_step">\n1.	Sit with your knees bent. Slightly lean your upper body back.\n2.	Stretch your arms in front of you, then pull your elbows back to make your elbows at a 90-degree angle and squeeze your shoulder blades. Repeat this exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="childs_pose_step">\n1.	Start in a kneeling position. Drop your butt toward your heels as you stretch the rest of your body down and forward.\n2.	In the fully stretched position, rest your arms in a relaxed position along the floor, rest your stomach comfortably on top of your thighs, and rest your forehead on the mat. Hold this position for 30 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="triceps_kickbacks_step">\n1.	Lean forward, bend your knees and your elbows. Extend your arms behind you and squeeze your triceps.\n2.	Please make your arms parallel to ground when extending them. Go back to the start position and repeat this exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="hip_hinge_step">\n1.	Stand upright with your feet shoulder width apart.\n2.	Sit your hips back and bend your upper body while keeping your upper body straight, then slowly go back to start position and repeat this exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="hover_push_ups_step">\n1.	Start in a push-up position. Lower yourself shift your body to left and then to right.\n2.	Push your body up and repeat this exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="swimmer_and_superman_step">\n1.	Lie on your stomach with your arms extended straight overhead. Alternately lift your opposite arm and leg.\n</string>
    <string name="hyperextension_step">\n1.	Lie down on your stomach with your toes touching the floor, and your chin on your hand.\n2.	Raise your chest up as high as possible off the floor. Hold this position for few seconds and then go back to the stat position. Repeat this exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="pike_push_ups_step">\n1.	Assume a push-up position on the floor. Your arms should be straight and your hands should be shoulder apart.\n2.	Now lift up your hips so that your body forms an upside- down V. Your legs and arms should stay as straight as possible.\n3.	Bend your elbows and lower your upper body until the top of your head nearly touches the floor. Pause, and then push yourself back up until your arms are straight.\n</string>
    <string name="reverse_push_ups_step">\n1.	Get into a normal push-up position, with your hands directly underneath your shoulders.\n2.	Lower yourself until your chest is an inch above the ground and push your body backward until your arms fully extend, with your knees bent and butt in the air.\n3.	Bring yourself back into the starting position and repeat this exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="supine_push_ups_step">\n1.	Lay down with your back flat on the floor. Feet also flat on the floor and your knees pointed up towards the ceiling.\n2.	Arms are out to your side even with shoulder height. Push up on your elbows and raise your upper back up off the ground.\n3.	Lower your upper back down to the floor and repeat this exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="reverse_snow_angels_step">\n1.	Place your forehead on the thick part of a mat or folded towel. Lie face down with your hands relaxed at your side.\n2.	Keeping your shoulders seated tightly in their socket and your arms locked out. Raise your hands overhead. Your hands and arms should remain a few inches off of the ground.\n3.	Move your hands to your sides. Keep your arms locked out and your shoulders remain seated tightly in their sockets and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="wall_calf_raises_step">\n1.	Stand straight with your hands on the wall and feet shoulder width apart.\n2.	Lift your heels and stand on your toes. Then drop your heels down. Repeat the exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="sumo_squat_calf_raises_with_wall_step">\n1.	Stand straight with your hands on the wall and your feet a little wider than shoulder width apart.\n2.	Lower your body until your thighs are parallel to the floor. Lift your heels up and down.\n</string>
    <string name="calf_stretch_left_step">\n1.	Stand one big step away in front of a wall. Step forward with your right foot and push the wall with your hands.\n2.	Please make sure your left leg is fully extended and you can feel your left calf stretching. Hold this position for a few seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="calf_stretch_right_step">\n1.	Stand one big step away in front of a wall. Step forward with your left foot and push the wall with your hands.\n2.	Please make sure your right leg is fully extended and you can feel your right calf stretching. Hold this position for a 30 seconds.\n</string>
    <string name="fire_hydrant_left_step">\n1.	Start on all fours with your knees under your butt and your hands under your shoulders. Then lift your left leg to the side at a 90 degree angle.\n</string>
    <string name="fire_hydrant_right_step">\n1.	Start on all fours with your knees under your butt and your hands under your shoulders. Then lift your right leg to the side at a 90 degree angle.\n</string>
    <string name="lunges_step">\n1.	Step forward with a leg and bend it until both legs are in a 90 degree angle. Make sure your body stays in a straight line on top of your rear knee.\n2.	Push through your front heel to activate your glutes and get back to the starting position.\n</string>
    <string name="side_leg_circles_left_step">\n1.	Lie on your right side with your head resting on your right hand.\n2.	Then lift your left leg and rotate your foot in circles.\n</string>
    <string name="side_leg_circles_right_step">\n1.	Lie on your left side with your head resting on your left hand.\n2.	Then lift your right leg and rotate your foot in circles.\n</string>
    <string name="sumo_squat_step">\n1.	Stand with your feet 6 – 12 inches apart. Stretch your arms in front of you.\n2.	Lower your body until your thighs are parallel to the floor. Return to the starting position and repeat the exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="reverse_flutter_kicks_step">\n1.	Lie facedown on a flat bench, positioning your hips on its edge. Your legs should be straight with your toes high off the floor with your arms on top of the bench. Hold onto the front edge.\n2.	Squeeze your glutes and hamstrings. Straighten your legs until they are level with your hips. This is the staring position.\n3.	Lift your left leg higher than your right leg. Lower your left leg as you lift the right one and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="wall_sit_step">\n1.	Keep your legs shoulder width apart and a 90 degree angle on your knees. Push your feet towards the floor and your back against the wall.\n</string>
    <string name="calf_raise_with_splayed_foot_step">\n1.	Stand with your feet shoulder width apart. Put your hands on the wall to maintain balance.\n2.	Twist your ankles to make your toes point outwards, then lift your heels up and down.\n</string>
    <string name="single_leg_calf_hop_left_step">\n1.	Stand straight with your right leg lifted. Then hop up and down on your left foot.\n</string>
    <string name="single_leg_calf_hop_right_step">\n1.	Stand straight with your left leg lifted. Then hop up and down on your right foot.\n</string>
    <string name="bottom_leg_lift_left_step">\n1.	Lie on your left side with your head resting on your left hand. Then put your right foot forward on the floor. Lift your left leg up and down.\n</string>
    <string name="bottom_leg_lift_right_step">\n1.	Lie on your right side with your head resting on your right hand. Then put your left foot forward on the floor. Lift your right leg up and down.\n</string>
    <string name="curtsy_lunges_step">\n1.	Step back diagonally with one leg at a time rear lunge position. Engage your core and keep your upper body straight.\n2.	Make sure your knees always stay behind your toes.\n</string>
    <string name="glute_kick_back_left_step">\n1.	Start on all fours with your knees under your butt and your hands directly under your shoulders.\n2.	Then kick with left leg back until it is parallel with the ground and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="glute_kick_back_right_step">\n1.	Start on all fours with your knees under your butt and your hands directly under your shoulders.\n2.	Then kick with right leg back until it is parallel with the ground and repeat.\n</string>
    <string name="lying_butterfly_stretch_step">\n1.	Lie on the floor with your feet together. Open your knees to the side. Hold this position.\n</string>
    <string name="leaning_stretcher_raises_step">\n1.	Stand a big step away from the wall, put your hands on the wall and lean on it.\n2.	Lift your heels as high as you can and then lower them down. Repeat this exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="wall_resisting_single_leg_calf_raise_left_step">\n1.	Stand a big step away from the wall. Put your right foot on your left ankle. Put your hands on the wall and lean on it.\n2.	Lift your left heel as high as you can and then lower it. Repeat this exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="wall_resisting_single_leg_calf_raise_right_step">\n1.	Stand a big step away from the wall. Put your left foot on your right ankle. Put your hands on the wall and lean on it.\n2.	Lift your right heel as high as you can and then lower it. Repeat this exercise.\n</string>


    //Workout Benefits
    <string name="abdominal_crunches_benefit">\n1.	It help you to relax and ease muscular stress and tension, it give you the six pack abs.\n2.	Crunches work on your abdominal muscles and help to strengthen your core.\n3.	Flexing your abdominal muscles on a daily basis will help you to lose weight and gain a flat belly, as well as great posture.\n4.	Abdominal crunches will also help to maintain the health of your spine.\n5.	If you are suffering from constipations, strengthening your abdominal press can severely benefit from these exercises.\n6.	A strong core is important for pregnant women. This type of exercise does not burn a lot of calories, however it will still increase your overall fitness.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_scissors_benefit">\n1.	Warms up and stretches the pectoral muscles, upper back muscles, shoulder muscles and upper arm muscles.\n2.	This exercise will tone your arms and provides strength.\n3.	It is one of the best cardio workouts to lose weight.\n</string>
    <string name="backward_lunges_benefit">\n1.	Lunges are an awesome exercise to tone the muscles of the lower body.\n2.	Backward lunges are safer for the knees because it’s much easier to emphasize the muscles of the gluts, hamstrings and quads.\n3.	Backward lunges help you focus more of your work on the large glute muscles.\n4.	Backward lunges are a great way to warm up and dynamically stretch your muscles.\n5.	Lung will help improve muscular strength and balance.\n</string>
    <string name="bicycle_crunches_benefit">\n1.	This exercise is for building core strength and toning your things.\n2.	If you want to lose weight, bicycle crunches are perfect because cycling is one of the most effective cardio exercise.\n3.	It improves muscle strength and mass.\n4.	It will help you develop the much in vogue six pack abs when clubbed with other exercises.\n</string>
    <string name="burpees_benefit">\n1.	Burpees will help you build discipline and mental toughness.\n2.	It will improve sports performance and physical skill.\n3.	It will make your skin glow.\n</string>
    <string name="cobra_stretch_benefit">\n1.	Stretches muscles in the shoulders, chest and abdominals.\n2.	Helps to ease symptoms of asthma.\n3.	Reduces belly fat and relieves stress.\n</string>
    <string name="forward_lunges_benefit">\n1.	Lunges are also an excellent way to develop your balance.\n2.	Lunges can improve your core strength.\n</string>
    <string name="inchworms_benefit">\n1.	The inchworm is a great bodyweight exercise that warms up the entire body.\n2.	Increases your balance and stability.\n</string>
    <string name="jumping_jack_benefit">\n1.	Warms up the whole body, loosening muscles in the legs, torso and arms.\n2.	It will improve your stamina, balance and stability.\n3.	It can relieve stress and also help improve flexibility.\n</string>
    <string name="jumping_squats_benefit">\n1.	This helps prevent heart diseases, hypertension and obesity.\n2.	Jump squats are the most effective exercise for weight loss.\n</string>
    <string name="mountain_climbers_benefit">\n1.	Mountain climbers require you to engage your upper arm muscles, as well as core and your legs.\n2.	They benefit muscular and cardiovascular fitness by increasing strength, flexibility and blood circulation.\n3.	They tone your butt and legs.\n</string>
    <string name="push_ups_benefit">\n1.	Push-ups burns a lot of calories as you are engaging multiple muscle groups at the same time.\n2.	Increasing upper body strength, primarily in chest, shoulders, arms and core.\n3.	Protects your shoulders from injury.\n</string>
    <string name="side_hop_benefit">\n1.	It will help you develop more explosive leg strength.\n2.	Side hops can help to increase your performance.\n3.	It increases aerobic fitness strengthens the heart and boosts your weight loss.\n</string>
    <string name="skipping_without_rope_benefit">\n1.	It is one of the best cardio and HIIT workout.\n2.	Skipping burns 1300 calories/hour calories in comparison to running.\n3.	It also helps in improving bone density.\n4.	Skipping is of the best ways to lose weight.\n</string>
    <string name="squats_benefit">\n1.	Squat exercise help build muscles throughout your body.\n2.	Good for digestion and help you to remove waste from the body.\n3.	Increases flexibility and burn more fat for weight loss.\n</string>
    <string name="incline_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	The incline push-up targets the lower portion of the pectorals major which helps improve the function of moving the arm to and from the center of the body, such as in a fly.\n2.	Increase blood flow to the upper body, helping to decrease post exercise soreness.\n</string>
    <string name="box_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	Improve your posture.\n2.	Enhance your cardiovascular system.\n3.	Protect your shoulders from injury.\n</string>
    <string name="knee_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	It strengthens the core, increase metabolic rate and reduce bone loss.\n2.	Build thigh muscles and protect from injury.\n</string>
    <string name="wide_arm_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	Push-ups remain one of the most effective exercises that help you to engage all your upper body getting stronger and fitter.\n2.	Your will burn more calories, this will help you make your stomach stronger and firmer.\n</string>
    <string name="chest_stertch_benefit">\n1.	Reduce soreness if your muscles are tight.\n2.	Better circulation to help recover from your workout.\n</string>
    <string name="side_lying_leg_lift_left_benefit">\n1.	It strengthens and builds up the hip muscles, helping them to look bigger and gives a more defined appearance.\n2.	This exercise is beneficial as it enhances posture, flexibility, balance and limb speed.\n</string>
    <string name="side_lying_leg_lift_right_benefit">\n1.	It strengthens and builds up the hip muscles, helping them to look bigger and gives a more defined appearance.\n2.	This exercise is beneficial as it enhances posture, flexibility, balance and limb speed.\n</string>
    <string name="donkey_kicks_left_benefit">\n1.	It helps in strengthening and lose the fat around your lower back.\n2.	It helps in reducing cellulite.\n3.	This exercise effectively targets and activates your glutes and firms and strengthens your butt and thighs.\n</string>
    <string name="donkey_kicks_right_benefit">\n1.	It helps in strengthening and loses the fat around your lower back.\n2.	It helps in reducing cellulite.\n3.	This exercise effectively targets and activates your glutes and firms and strengthens your butt and thighs.\n</string>
    <string name="left_quad_stretch_with_wall_benefit">\n1.	Quad stretch with wall stretches reduces stress, improved circulation and increased flexibility.\n2.	Leg stretches when done properly can reduced the risk of injury, strengthen the muscles and improve stamina.\n</string>
    <string name="right_quad_stretch_with_wall_benefit">\n1.	Quad stretch with wall stretches reduces stress, improved circulation and increased flexibility.\n2.	Leg stretches when done properly can reduced the risk of injury, strengthen the muscles and improve stamina.\n</string>
    <string name="knee_to_chest_stretch_left_benefit">\n1.	Stretches and stabilizes the pelvis and low back and can reduce lower back pain.\n2.	Reduces excessive anger, excitement, anxiety and high blood pressure.\n</string>
    <string name="knee_to_chest_stretch_right_benefit">\n1.	Stretches and stabilizes the pelvis and low back and can reduce lower back pain.\n2.	Reduces excessive anger, excitement, anxiety and high blood pressure.\n</string>
    <string name="hindu_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	Improve body flexibility, practicing both upward facing dog position and downward dog facing position in a single exercise can give incredible results in your spine flexibility.\n2.	As this exercise involves moving your body up and down, your heart rate gets increased. When your heart is busy pumping blood, it functions.\n</string>
    <string name="staggered_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	Strength exercises create muscle mass and builds strength in your body.\n2.	This is an advanced push-up variation since it incorporates more core, shoulder and triceps stability, thus more strength in your rotator cuffs. Because you are in motion, strength push-ups exercises engage the core movement muscles more than the core stabilization muscles.\n3.	It also helps to tone the body, by assisting in quick unwanted weight and fat loss.\n4.	Staggered push-ups also helps to improve the cardiovascular system of the body.\n</string>
    <string name="push_ups_and_rotation_benefit">\n1.	It will optimize your coordination and build your sense of balance.\n2.	The main purpose and intent of pushups with rotation is to provide a high amount of physical challenge to body.\n3.	Many athletes who play sports that involves consistent rotation of the torso can profit from rotational push-ups.\n4.	You are not only strengthening your core muscles for stabilization but also increasing your neuromuscular control to maintain balance.\n</string>
    <string name="decline_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	Decline pushups can help replace chest files if you travel on vacation or business and don’t have time to find set of weights.\n2.	Increasing mobility in hips and shoulders as well as stepping up the challenge of exercise.\n3.	The only equipment require is table, chair, stability ball or other sturdy, raised surface upon which you rest your feet.\n4.	This allows you to perform the exercise without needing specialized equipment , so it’s easy to do at a park or in a hotel room.\n</string>
    <string name="spiderman_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	It helps your chest and arm muscles work harder. When you move your leg forward , it shifts your weight , which means that your muscles have to adjust to the new position.\n2.	This helps to work different muscle groups , increasing the resistance and helping you strengthen your  muscles more quickly.\n3.	As with most forms of pushups, spiderman pushups mainly works your pectoral muscles , your deltoids and your triceps. It also can engage your core muscles and helps to strengthen them.\n4.	Maintaining balance on three points forces your abs and core muscles to work overtime.\n</string>
    <string name="russian_twist_benefit">\n1.	There is more to doing the seated Russian twist than a flat stomach or a six pack abdomen. The exercise works more than just your abdomen.\n2.	It reduces the risk of cardiovascular diseases like strokes and heart attacks.\n3.	A strengthened abdominal muscle helps to prevent slouching and get a good posture.\n4.	A trimmed abdomen also helps you in your everyday activities like bending to put your shoe , pick up something from the floor, etc.\n5.	This exercise really works the upper core and oblique muscles due to twisting motion.\n</string>
    <string name="heel_touch_benefit">\n1.	This exercise focus on the angled muscles.\n2.	It is a solid , minimal exercise that makes a solid compression on the slanted muscles. It will help create portability, steadiness and adaptability in the hips and lower back.\n3.	Keep your breathing predictable.\n4.	Your back ought to be kept level on the floor with your neck lose. Try not to worry your body or hunch advances or twist your shoulders.\n</string>
    <string name="leg_raises_benefit">\n1.	Helps to lower your risk for back injuries, back pain and back strain while performing other exercise or routine activities.\n2.	All types of leg raises increase the flexibility , agility and strength of the hip flexors. Supports the lower back and improves your flexibility.\n3.	This exercise not only makes you stronger but healthier as well. It helps in digestion , absorption of nutrients and elimination of toxins from your body.\n</string>
    <string name="plank_benefit">\n1.	Planks require your arms, your legs, and your abs , making them an all-encompassing workout and a more efficient way to exercise.\n2.	Planks help to improve your posture.\n3.	Planks also helps you develop isometric strength in your core muscles, which gives you the power to keep from hunching while standing or sitting for long periods of time.\n</string>
    <string name="spine_lumber_twist_strech_left_benefit">\n1.	Twists bring blood flow and nutrients to the spines , hips and shoulders.\n2.	Twists stretched the hips, glutes, abs, oblique, back, chest, shoulder and neck.\n3.	Twists increase range of motion in the upper body and alleviate lower back and shoulder pain.\n4.	Twists can help to correct poor posture an improve breathing.\n</string>
    <string name="spine_lumber_twist_strech_right_benefit">\n1.	Twists bring blood flow and nutrients to the spine, hips and shoulders.\n2.	Twists stretch  the hips, glutes, abs, oblique, back, chest, shoulders and neck.\n3.	Twists increase range of motion in the upper body and alleviate lower back and shoulder pain.\n4.	Twists can help to correct poor posture an improve breathing.\n</string>
    <string name="crossover_crunch_benefit">\n1.	Crunches help improve your balance by strengthening your abdominal muscles.\n2.	Strong core muscles improve your posture, which helps you function efficiently in everyday life and in sporting event.\n3.	A healthy posture also helps prevent lower back pain and muscle injury.\n</string>
    <string name="side_bridges_left_benefit">\n1.	The side bridge is an excellent exercise for the abdominals and for training trunk stabilization.\n2.	It is one tool to help improve force transmission from the lower to the upper body, as well as improve posture and reduce the risk of back injuries.\n3.	Help build core strength and correct your posture.\n4.	Improve stamina and stability.\n5.	Reduce knee and back pain.\n6.	Tone the lower body.\n</string>
    <string name="side_bridges_right_benefit">\n1.	The side bridge is an excellent exercise for the abdominals and for training trunk stabilization.\n2.	It is one tool to help improve force transmission from the lower to the upper body, as well as improve posture and reduce the risk of back injuries.\n3.	Help build core strength and correct your posture.\n4.	Improve stamina and stability.\n5.	Reduce knee and back pain.\n6.	Tone the lower body.\n</string>
    <string name="butt_bridge_benefit">\n1.	The side bridge is an excellent exercise for the abdominals and for training trunk stabilization.\n2.	It is one tool to help improve force transmission from the lower to the upper body, as well as improve posture and reduce the risks of back injuries.\n3.	Help build core strength and correct your posture.\n4.	Improve stamina and stability.\n5.	Reduce stamina and stability.\n6.	Tone the lower body.\n</string>
    <string name="v_up_benefit">\n1.	V-ups are an effective exercise for toning upper and lower abdominal muscles. They tone your rectus abdominal muscle and gives you classic 6 packs abs.\n2.	This exercise strengthens the lower back muscles and tightness the thighs.\n3.	They also helps in toning muscles of your arms and legs.\n4.	They can help you in improving your balance.\n</string>
    <string name="side_plank_left_benefit">\n1.	Side plank requires you to balance on one arm, so this is a great pose for strengthening your shoulders, wrists, and arms.\n2.	Improves the stability of core complex and reduces lower back pain.\n3.	Increase muscular endurance in the lower back.\n4.	This oblique workout at home is a great way to test how strong your core is by seeing how long you can hold this pose.\n5.	Strengthens the abdominal muscles.\n6.	Improves balance and concentration.\n</string>
    <string name="side_plank_right_benefit">\n1.	Side plank requires you to balance on one arm, so this is a great pose for strengthening your shoulders, wrists, and arms.\n2.	Improves the stability of core complex and reduces lower back pain.\n3.	Increase muscular endurance in the lower back.\n4.	This oblique workout at home is a great way to test how strong your core is by seeing how long you can hold this pose.\n5.	Strengthens the abdominal muscles.\n6.	Improves balance and concentration.\n</string>
    <string name="sit_ups_benefit">\n1.	Sit ups will help you look better by burning calories and ripping your abs, sit ups also greatly help to increase your flexibility and range of motion. These two benefits can help a person have better posture and reduce the risk of getting a back strain or injury.\n2.	Easily modified.\n3.	Sit ups will help the circulation of blood in the abdomen and hips. Both of these body parts will maintain the various systems are very important for health as digestion and immunity.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_raises_benefit">\n1.	It improves digestion.\n2.	It stretches and tones the muscles of the abdomen.\n3.	It expands the chest and the rib cage resulting in full intake of oxygen. The lung capacity is fully utilized.\n4.	Release tension and increase flexibility of arms.\n</string>
    <string name="side_arm_raises_benefit">\n1.	Side arm are stronger, larger shoulders and increased shoulder mobility.\n2.	It loosens the muscles of the chest.\n3.	This exercise also helps to open up the chest and align the shoulder blades, improving posture and increasing flexibility.\n4.	Increasing shoulder size and growth is the key to any strength, power, and fitness athlete as it allows the newly built muscle.\n</string>
    <string name="triceps_dips_benefit">\n1.	Triceps become stronger with this exercise, the strength and stability of your shoulders and elbows increases.\n2.	The functionality, flexibility and range of motion of your arm increases the more you work and strengthen these muscles.\n3.	Dips are also great way of making your joints stronger – your wrist, elbow, shoulder joint are all involved in this exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_circles_clockwise_benefit">\n1.	This exercise sending oxygen rich blood to the throwing muscles, improving your flexibility and giving an isolated workout to the rotator cuff muscles.\n2.	This exercise loosen all the muscles that are required in throwing motion, from your chest and back to your shoulders and arms.\n3.	Reduces body fat and also helps to warm the body.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_circles_counter_clockwise_benefit">\n1.	This exercise sending oxygen rich blood to the throwing muscles, improving your flexibility and giving an isolated workout to the rotator cuff muscles.\n2.	This exercise loosen all the muscles that are required in throwing motion, from your chest and back to your shoulders and arms.\n3.	Reduces body fat and also helps to warm the body.\n</string>
    <string name="diamond_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	You are targeting your full chest. Your triceps will be strong and your front deltoids will be strong. Your nervous system will reprogram your body and mind to function better this way.\n2.	Solid triceps and chest strength. Also great for the upper chest development.\n3.	Great core strength and no lower back pain.\n4.	Overall beautiful athletic body is what you will build.\n5.	Your body muscles need more oxygen to produce energy to sustain you through this exercise and that can only be achieved by getting the heart to pump blood faster.\n6.	Diamond push-ups greatly aid in burning large amount of calories in the body, particularly in the mid section.\n</string>
    <string name="leg_barbell_curl_left_benefit">\n1.	Barbells improve athletic performance.\n2.	It not just helps in developing an impressive looking arm but also increases grip strength and makes your biceps less prone to injury.\n3.	Aid the development of strong bones and increase stamina.\n4.	Help manage chronic conditions.\n5.	Help to reduce injuries and stress.\n</string>
    <string name="leg_barbell_curl_right_benefit">\n1.	Barbells improve athletic performance.\n2.	It not just helps in developing an impressive looking arm but also increases grip strength and makes your biceps less prone to injury.\n3.	Aid the development of strong bones and increase stamina.\n4.	Help manage chronic conditions.\n5.	Help to reduce injuries and stress.\n</string>
    <string name="diagonal_plank_benefit">\n1.	Planks will improve your balance and posture.\n2.	Planks help get rid of back pain.\n3.	Planks improve your flexibility and mood.\n4.	Planking will improve your metabolism.\n</string>
    <string name="wall_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	Wall push-ups are an effective exercise for those looking to develop strength in their chest, shoulders and triceps.\n2.	It works out the upper body and your core muscles.\n3.	Wall push-ups are an excellent option for beginners who cannot support their body weight or pregnant women who cannot lie on their stomachs.\n4.	Improved posture and the ability to complete everyday tasks with more ease.\n</string>
    <string name="triceps_stretch_left_benefit">\n1.	Triceps become stronger with these exercises, the strength and stability of your shoulders and elbows increase. The functionality, flexibility and range of motion of your arm increases the more you work and strengthen these muscles.\n2.	Dips are also a great way of making your joints stronger.\n3.	Dips are advanced exercise that focuses the triceps involving shoulder joint as well as the elbow. It is one of the great travel exercises and requires no equipment.\n4.	As mentioned earlier, it can be done easily with the aid of chair and bench. They are the challenging upper body strengthening exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="triceps_stretch_right_benefit">\n1.	Triceps become stronger with these exercises, the strength and stability of your shoulders and elbows increase. The functionality, flexibility and range of motion of your arm increases the more you work and strengthen these muscles.\n2.	Dips are also a great way of making your joints stronger.\n3.	Dips are advanced exercise that focuses the triceps involving shoulder joint as well as the elbow. It is one of the great travel exercises and requires no equipment.\n4.	As mentioned earlier, it can be done easily with the aid of chair and bench. They are the challenging upper body strengthening exercise.\n</string>
    <string name="standing_biceps_stretch_left_benefit">\n1.	These biceps stretch will help improve and maintain the function of muscle.\n2.	The biceps has attachments in the shoulder complex and hence, can also help with your shoulder and chest function.\n3.	By taking time to perform this, it will help in the prevention of not only bicep injury, but also reduce your chances of hurting your shoulders or chest.\n4.	To improve the range and increase muscle strength and flexibility, make sure that you always stretch your biceps after an upper body workout routine.\n</string>
    <string name="standing_biceps_stretch_right_benefit">\n1.	These biceps stretch will help improve and maintain the function of muscle.\n2.	The biceps has attachments in the shoulder complex and hence, can also help with your shoulder and chest function.\n3.	By taking time to perform this, it will help in the prevention of not only bicep injury, but also reduce your chances of hurting your shoulders or chest.\n4.	To improve the range and increase muscle strength and flexibility, make sure that you always stretch your biceps after an upper body workout routine.\n</string>
    <string name="floor_triceps_dips_benefit">\n1.	The benefits of these exercises are increased strength and flexibility in your triceps.\n</string>
    <string name="military_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	Helps build strength and muscles.\n2.	Helps in increasing stamina, flexibility.\n</string>
    <string name="alternating_hooks_benefit">\n1.	Increases heart rate and oxygen circulation supply. Hence, making heart and lungs strong and healthy.\n2.	Helps build upper body strength.\n3.	Develop self defense skills and builds self-esteem and confidence.\n4.	Improves on your stamina and endurance.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_curl_crunch_left_benefit">\n1.	Reduce neck and back pain and stretching arms.\n2.	An improvement to your flexibility and range of movement.\n3.	Arm curls can also reduce stress, soreness, muscle, fatigue and injury.\n</string>
    <string name="arm_curl_crunch_right_benefit">\n1.	Reduce neck and back pain and stretching arms.\n2.	An improvement to your flexibility and range of movement.\n3.	Arm curls can also reduce stress, soreness, muscle, fatigue and injury.\n</string>
    <string name="shoulder_gators_benefit">\n1.	Helps increase strength, flexibility, stamina.\n</string>
    <string name="doorway_curls_left_benefit">\n1.	It helps to make stronger leg, arms and shoulder.\n2.	It also helps to better balance.\n</string>
    <string name="doorway_curls_right_benefit">\n1.	It helps to make stronger leg, arms and shoulder.\n2.	It also helps to better balance.\n</string>
    <string name="modified_push_ups_low_hold_benefit">\n1.	It helps to toning your arms, chest, shoulders and core.\n2.	They train you for full push-ups and make your chest and upper back strong.\n3.	It burn about 100 calories for every 10 minutes you are working.\n</string>
    <string name="rhomboid_pulls_benefit">\n1.	This is not only for aim at rhomboid but they also shape up adjacent muscles and make them strong.\n2.	Prevent back and neck pain, rounding of shoulders and a curved back.\n3.	This makes muscles more flexible and improves blood flow in the area.\n4.	Benefits people suffering from acute pain in or around the shoulder or upper back area.\n</string>
    <string name="side_lying_floor_strerch_left_benefit">\n1.	Helps in blood circulation.\n2.	Increases stamina, focus.\n</string>
    <string name="side_lying_floor_strerch_right_benefit">\n1.	Helps in blood circulation.\n2.	Increases stamina, focus.\n</string>
    <string name="cat_cow_pose_benefit">\n1.	Increases flexibility of the neck, shoulders and spine. The movement also stretches the muscles of the hips, back, abdomen, chest and lungs.\n2.	Allows more coordinated physical movement.\n3.	It stimulates your kidneys and adrenal glands.\n4.	It calms you down and relieves stress.\n5.	Improves posture and balance.\n</string>
    <string name="reclined_rhomboid_squeezes_benefit">\n1.	Increase blood circulation.\n2.	Increase stamina, strength, focus.\n</string>
    <string name="childs_pose_benefit">\n1.	Stretches the lower back, shoulders, hips, ankles, and thighs.\n2.	It’s great for your digestion.\n3.	It promotes blood circulation all throughout the body.\n4.	Helps to reduce stress and anxiety.\n5.	Reduce back and neck pain.\n</string>
    <string name="triceps_kickbacks_benefit">\n1.	It helps to sculpt and tone your arms.\n2.	Increases your physical strength and also help to trim body fat.\n3.	The triceps kickback makes it possible for you to train this hard to isolate muscle group.\n4.	It helps to reduce in lower back pain.\n</string>
    <string name="hip_hinge_benefit">\n1.	Helps to make stronger lower back and get rounder butt.\n2.	Athletes can get strong in this position and increases their performance.\n3.	Performing the hip-hinge is a great way to build the gluteus muscles and loss the fat.\n</string>
    <string name="hover_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	Increase blood circulation.\n2.	Increases stamina, strength, focus.\n</string>
    <string name="swimmer_and_superman_benefit">\n1.	Builds support and stability for the spine, and it can also prevent and reduce back pain.\n2.	Increased lower back and glute development.\n3.	Improves stability and control fitness movements.\n</string>
    <string name="hyperextension_benefit">\n1.	Improves posture by lengthening the back muscles and reducing the tension in the lower back and core area.\n2.	Increases functional strength and physical performance.\n3.	Reduce back pain.\n4.	Stronger lower back.\n5.	Enhances physical ability.\n6.	Helps improve figure.\n</string>
    <string name="pike_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	This workout is great for the back of the shoulders, the core, the back, and the hamstrings.\n2.	They are a great accolade to any upper body workout os shoulder workout.\n3.	They are adjustable to almost any fitness level.\n4.	Great exercise for building shoulder strength and improving core stability.\n</string>
    <string name="reverse_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	Helps to improve strength, stamina.\n2.	Increases flexibility in the shoulders, spine and back.\n</string>
    <string name="supine_push_ups_benefit">\n1.	Improves blood circulation, focus.\n2.	Increases stamina, strength.\n</string>
    <string name="reverse_snow_angels_benefit">\n1.	This exercise that helps reduces shoulder pain.\n2.	Restrictions and improve the ability of the scapula (shoulder blades to glide properly) with good arm mechanics.\n</string>
    <string name="wall_calf_raises_benefit">\n1.	The calf muscles support your ankle. When you improve ankle stability, you improve balance.\n2.	Your calf muscles control your ankle motion.\n3.	Calf raise is an excellent exercise to train leg muscles. The development of these muscles helps to form a proportional figure and strengthen the ankle.\n4.	Women like to wear skirts and tight pants, so workout for legs are extremely important.\n</string>
    <string name="sumo_squat_calf_raises_with_wall_benefit">\n1.	Squats are arguably the best exercise for your entire body, a functional exercise which allows you to build muscle whilst burning any idle fats which are stored in your body.\n2.	When performed properly, squats can improve your entire body composition – including the areas around your knees.\n3.	Strong legs are crucial for maintaining balance and mobility, especially as you get older. Sumo squats help to strengthen your overall core and body.\n4.	You’ll burn more fat by doing more squats.\n5.	Tones and lifts the Butt.\n</string>
    <string name="calf_stretch_left_benefit">\n1.	Warms up and stretches the calf muscles.\n2.	Calf stretches can also prevent injuries of the feet and reduce the chances of chronic back pain and knee problem.\n3.	Not to forget that stretches can relax both the body and mind and release tension and stress.\n4.	Regular calf stretches help maintain  your body’s mobility.\n5.	Increase circulation to your lower extremity.\n6.	Decreased frequency of leg cramps.\n</string>
    <string name="calf_stretch_right_benefit">\n1.	Warms up and stretches the calf muscles.\n2.	Calf stretches can also prevent injuries of the feet and reduce the chances of chronic back pain and knee problem.\n3.	Not to forget that stretches can relax both the body and mind and release tension and stress.\n4.	Regular calf stretches help maintain  your body’s mobility.\n5.	Increase circulation to your lower extremity.\n6.	Decreased frequency of leg cramps.\n</string>
    <string name="fire_hydrant_left_benefit">\n1.	Fire hydrant exercise strengthens the lower body, improves balance, increases the mobility of the hip and knee joints, correct posture, activate abdominal muscles, and increases the muscle tonus.\n2.	Fire hydrant exercise is particularly beneficial for the hips, inner thighs and buttocks.\n3.	It also help to stretch the hip joints and inner thighs.\n4.	Stretching after fire hydrant exercise will improve muscle flexibility, the amplitude of movements, and make the muscles stronger.\n</string>
    <string name="fire_hydrant_right_benefit">\n1.	Fire hydrant exercise strengthens the lower body, improves balance, increases the mobility of the hip and knee joints, correct posture, activate abdominal muscles, and increases the muscle tonus.\n2.	Fire hydrant exercise is particularly beneficial for the hips, inner thighs and buttocks.\n3.	It also help to stretch the hip joints and inner thighs.\n4.	Stretching after fire hydrant exercise will improve muscle flexibility, the amplitude of movements, and make the muscles stronger.\n</string>
    <string name="lunges_benefit">\n1.	Lunges are really great bodyweight exercise that will strengthen your muscles and tone them at the same time.\n2.	Lunges are also an excellent way to develop your balance.\n3.	Lunges can improve your core strength.\n4.	Relieves lower back pain and improves your balance, posture, stability and athletic performance.\n5.	Lunges are a remarkable way to bring some flexibility to the hip and thigh muscles.\n</string>
    <string name="side_leg_circles_left_benefit">\n1.	Increases core strength and hip mobility.\n</string>
    <string name="side_leg_circles_right_benefit">\n1.	Increases core strength and hip mobility.\n</string>
    <string name="sumo_squat_benefit">\n1.	Squats are arguably the best exercise for your entire body, a functional exercise which allows you to build muscle whilst burning any idle fats which are stored in your body.\n2.	When performed properly, squats can improve your entire body composition – including the areas around your knees.\n3.	Strong legs are crucial for maintaining balance and mobility, especially as you get older. Sumo squats help to strengthen your overall core and body.\n4.	You’ll burn more fat by doing more squats.\n5.	Tones and lifts the Butt.\n</string>
    <string name="reverse_flutter_kicks_benefit">\n1.	Flutter kicks are great calorie burner. Depending on your current body weight and exercise duration and intensity, you can burn anywhere between 20-120 calories.\n2.	Flutter kicks also engage and activate the muscles  in your thighs.\n3.	Improves posture and reduces back pain.\n4.	The flutter kick helps relax the various muscles it works on, such as the abs, glutes, and inner and outer thighs. This, in turn, improves your flexibility.\n</string>
    <string name="wall_sit_benefit">\n1.	Wall sit on a daily basis is that they will help you achieve those 6 or even 8 pack abs that those male models in the magazines have.\n2.	Wall sits help you learn concentration and focus.\n3.	They will help you better balance.\n4.	Increasing your stamina and physical performance.\n</string>
    <string name="calf_raise_with_splayed_foot_benefit">\n1.	One of the benefits of calf raises is improved muscular strength.\n2.	Make a stronger leg.\n</string>
    <string name="single_leg_calf_hop_left_benefit">\n1.	One of the benefits of single leg calf hop left is improved muscular strength.\n2.	Make a stronger leg.\n</string>
    <string name="single_leg_calf_hop_right_benefit">\n1.	One of the benefits of single leg calf hop right is improved muscular strength.\n2.	Make a stronger leg.\n</string>
    <string name="bottom_leg_lift_left_benefit">\n1.	Make a stronger leg.\n2.	It helps to reduce fat on thigh.\n3.	Leg lift helps to lower your risk for black injuries, black pain and back strain while performing other exercises or routine activities.\n4.	If you play sports, building these muscles also helps you increase your agility and endurance on the playing field by helping you stabilize fast direction changes and helps you maintain balance.\n</string>
    <string name="bottom_leg_lift_right_benefit">\n1.	Make a stronger leg.\n2.	It helps to reduce fat on thigh.\n3.	Leg lift helps to lower your risk for black injuries, black pain and back strain while performing other exercises or routine activities.\n4.	If you play sports, building these muscles also helps you increase your agility and endurance on the playing field by helping you stabilize fast direction changes and helps you maintain balance.\n</string>
    <string name="curtsy_lunges_benefit">\n1.	Curtsy luges target your inner thighs as well as your glute medias, a smaller butt muscle that helps stabilize hips to help improve your posture.\n2.	Regular and proper performance will bring you excellent results – your legs and glutes will be toned and beautiful.\n3.	You will become stronger, healthier and happier.\n4.	Lunge are phenomenal for increasing leg strength.\n</string>
    <string name="glute_kick_back_left_benefit">\n1.	Increases flexibility in the gluteal muscles.\n</string>
    <string name="glute_kick_back_right_benefit">\n1.	Increases flexibility in the gluteal muscles.\n</string>
    <string name="lying_butterfly_stretch_benefit">\n1.	Increases flexibility in the inner thighs, hips and groins.\n2.	Helps in smooth delivery if practiced regular until late pregnancy.\n3.	A good stretch for the inner thighs, groins and knees, improving flexibility in the groin and hip region.\n4.	Stimulates the heart and improves general circulation.\n5.	Keeps the reproductive system healthy.\n</string>
    <string name="leaning_stretcher_raises_benefit">\n1.	Increases flexibility in the inner thighs, hips and groins.\n2.	Helps in smooth delivery if practiced regular until late pregnancy.\n3.	A good stretch for the inner thighs, groins and knees, improving flexibility in the groin and hip region.\n4.	Stimulates the heart and improves general circulation.\n5.	Keeps the reproductive system healthy.\n</string>
    <string name="wall_resisting_single_leg_calf_raise_left_benefit">\n1.	Make a stronger leg.\n2.	It helps to reduce fat on thigh.\n3.	It helps to lower your risk for black injuries, black pain and back strain while performing other exercises or routine activities.\n4.	If you play sports, building these muscles also helps you increase your agility and endurance on the playing field by helping you stabilize fast direction changes and helps you maintain balance.\n</string>
    <string name="wall_resisting_single_leg_calf_raise_right_benefit">\n1.	Make a stronger leg.\n2.	It helps to reduce fat on thigh.\n3.	It helps to lower your risk for black injuries, black pain and back strain while performing other exercises or routine activities.\n4.	If you play sports, building these muscles also helps you increase your agility and endurance on the playing field by helping you stabilize fast direction changes and helps you maintain balance.\n</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->


</resources>